Guide to the Bruce J. Zobel Papers, 1937-2008 MC 00259
Special Collections Research Center
- Symposia and Conferences, 1937-1993; MC 00259 Series 11
  - Tree Improvement Conferences
    - Southern
      - Proceedings of the Third Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Held at New Orleans, Louisiana, January 5-6, 1955. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, May, 1955; Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 12)
      - Proceedings of the Fourth Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Held in Athens, Georgia, January 8-9, 1957., Formerly Box 64L (Box 137, Folder 13)
      - Proceedings of the Fifth Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Held in Raleigh, North Carolina. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1959; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 1)
      - Proceedings of the Sixth Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Gainesville, Florida. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1961; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 2)
      - Proceedings of the Seventh Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Gulfport, Mississippi. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1963; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 3)
      - Proceedings of the Eighth Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Held in Savannah, Georgia, June 16-17, 1965. Macon, Georgia: Committee on Southern Forest Tree Improvement, May, 1966; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 4)
      - Proceedings of the Ninth Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Knoxville, Tennessee. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1967; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 5)
      - Proceedings of the Tenth Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Houston, Texas. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1969; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 6)
      - Abstracts of the Eleventh Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Atlanta, Georgia. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1971; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 7)
      - Proceedings of the Eleventh Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Atlanta, Georgia. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1971; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 8)
      - Proceedings of the Twelfth Southern Conference on Forest Tree Improvement. Baton Rouge, Louisiana. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1973; Formerly Box 64M (Box 138, Folder 9)
      - Proceedings of the Thirteenth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Raleigh, North Carolina. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1975; Formerly Box 64N (Box 139, Folder 1)
      - Proceedings of the Fifteenth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Mississippi State University. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1979; Formerly Box 64N (Box 139, Folder 2)
      - Abstracts of the Fifteenth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Mississippi State University. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1979; Formerly Box 64N (Box 139, Folder 3)
      - Proceedings of the Sixteenth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Blacksburg, Virginia. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1981; Formerly Box 64N (Box 139, Folder 4)
      - Proceedings of the Seventeenth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. University of Georgia. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1983; Formerly Box 64N (Box 139, Folder 5)
      - Proceedings of the Twentieth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Charleston, South Carolina. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1989; Formerly Box 64N (Box 139, Folder 6)
      - Abstracts of the Twentieth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Charleston, South Carolina. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1989; Formerly Box 64N (Box 139, Folder 7)
      - S-23 Workshop Reprints, Baton Rouge, Louisiana, 1984; Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 1)
      - Conference Information and Abstracts of the Twenty-fourth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Orlando, Florida. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1997; Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 2)
      - Proceedings of the Twenty-fourth Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Orlando, Florida. Southern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1997; Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 3)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Proceedings of First Noranda Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at MacMillan Bloedel Inc., Pine Hill, Alabama, February 27-28, 1990, Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 4)
      - "Proceedings of the June 1973 Meeting of the Western Hemlock Tree Improvement Committee." Industrial Forestry Association IFA Tree Improvement Newsletter. No. 20, January 1974; Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 5)
      - Proceedings of the 16th Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at Macdonald College, Quebec, Canada, August 8-10, 1968. Upper Darby, Pennsylvania: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, U.S. Forest Service, 1969; Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 6)
      - Fins, L. Progress Report of the Inland Empire Cooperative Forest Tree Improvement Program. Moscow, Idaho: University of Idaho, August, 1980; Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 7)
      - Fins, L. Eighth Progress Report of the Inland Empire Cooperative Forest Tree Improvement Program. Moscow, Idaho: University of Idaho, August, 1984; Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 8)
      - Fins, Lauren. Tenth Progress Report of the Inland Empire Cooperative Forest Tree Improvement Program. Moscow, Idaho: University of Idaho, October, 1986; Formerly Box 64P (Box 140, Folder 9)
      - Bound copies of the Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference Proceedings, Vol. 1-7, 1953-1959; Formerly Box 64Q (Box 141, Folder 1)
      - Bound copies of the Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference Proceedings, Vol. 8-15, 1960-1967; Formerly Box 64Q (Box 141, Folder 2)
      - Bound copies of the Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference Proceedings, Vol. 16-20, 1968-1972; Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 1)
        plus Cumulative Index for Vols. 1-20
      - Proceedings of the 30th Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at the School of Forest Resources, the University of Maine, Department of Forest Biology, Orono, Maine, July 22-24, 1986. Durham, New Hampshire: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1987; Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 2)
      - Western Forest Genetics Association Annual Meeting. Held in Moscow, Idaho, August 3, 1967, Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 3)
      - Proceedings of the Lake States Forest Genetics Conference. Held March 31-April 1, 1953. Miscellaneous Report No. 22. Lake States Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, [no date], Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 4)
      - Proceedings of the Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held August 30-31, 1955. Miscellaneous Report No. 40. Lake States Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, December, 1955; Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 5)
      - Proceedings of the Third Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held September 17-18, 1957. Station Paper No. 58. Lake States Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, February, 1958; Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 6)
      - Proceedings of the Fourth Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held October 6-7, 1959. Station Paper No. 81. Lake States Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, April, 1960; Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 7)
      - Proceedings of the Fifth Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held September 19-20, 1961. Station Paper No. 98. Lake States Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, April, 1962; Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 8)
      - Proceedings of the Sixth Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held September 9-10, 1963. Lake States Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, August, 1964; Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 9)
      - Joint Proceedings of the Second Genetics Workshop of the Society of American Foresters and the Seventh Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held October 21-23, 1965. Research Paper NC-6. Central Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, July, 1966; Formerly Box 64R (Box 142, Folder 10)
      - Proceedings of the Eighth Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held September 12-13, 1967. Research Paper NC-23. North Central Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, 1968; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 1)
      - Proceedings of the Ninth Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held August 22-23, 1969. Research Paper NC-47. North Central Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, 1970; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 2)
      - Joint Proceedings of the Tenth Lake States Forest Tree Improvement Conference and the Seventh Central States Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held September 22-24, 1971. General Technical Report NC-3. North Central Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, 1973; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 3)
      - Proceedings of the Twelfth Lake States Forest Tree Improvement. Held August 1975. General Technical Report NC-26. North Central Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, 1976; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 4)
      - Proceedings of the Thirteenth Lake States Forest Tree Improvement. Held at the University of Minnesota, St. Paul, MN, August 17-18, 1977. General Technical Report NC-50. North Central Forest Experiment Station, U.S.D.A. Forest Service, 1979; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 5)
      - Proceedings of the 21st Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at the University of New Brunswick, Fredericton, New Brunswick, Canada, August 27-30, 1973. Upper Darby, Pennsylvania: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1974; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 6)
      - Proceedings of the 22nd Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at the State University of New York, College of Environmental Science and Forestry, Syracuse, New York, August 7-9, 1974. Upper Darby, Pennsylvania: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1975; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 7)
      - Proceedings of the 23rd Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at Rutgers University, Cook College, New Brunswick, New Jersey, August 4-7, 1975. Upper Darby, Pennsylvania: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1976; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 8)
      - Proceedings of the 24th Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at the University of Maryland, Center for Environmental and Estuarine Studies, College Park, Maryland, July 26-27, 1976. Upper Darby, Pennsylvania: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1977; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 9)
      - Proceedings of the 27th Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at the School of Natural Resources, the University of Vermont, Burlington, Vermont, July 29-31, 1980. Durham, New Hampshire: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1981; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 10)
      - Proceedings of the 28th Northeastern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Held at the Institute of Natural and Environmental Resources, University of New Hampshire, Durham, New Hampshire, July 7-9, 1982. Durham, New Hampshire: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, 1983; Formerly Box 64S (Box 143, Folder 11)
  - Vegetative Propagation
    - Vegetative propagation of forest trees-physiology and practice. Lectures from a symposium in Uppsala, Sweden, February 16-17, 1977. The Institute for Forest Improvement and The Department of Forest Genetics, College of Forestry, The Swedish University of Agricultural Sciences, Formerly Box 64T (Box 144, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of the Southern Containerized Forest Tree Seedling Conference. Held in Savannah, Georgia, August 25-27, 1981. Edited by Richard W. Guldin and James P. Barnett. New Orleans, Louisiana: USDA Forest Service, Southern Forest Experiment Station, June, 1982; Formerly Box 64T (Box 144, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of Flowering and Seed Development in Trees: a Symposium. Held at Mississippi State University, May 15-18, 1978. Edited by Frank Bonner. Starkville, Mississippi, 1979; Formerly Box 64T (Box 144, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of Southeastern Area Forest Nurserymen Conferences. Held in Columbia, SC, August 23-24, 1966 and in Hot Springs, Arkansas, August 30-31, 1966, Formerly Box 64T (Box 144, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of Region 8 Forest Nurserymen's Conferences. Held in Morganton, NC, August 19-20, 1964 and in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, September 16-17, 1964, Formerly Box 64T (Box 144, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the 1984 Southern Nursery Conferences. Held in Alexandria, Louisiana, June 11-14, 1984 and in Asheville, North Carolina, July 24-27, 1984, Formerly Box 64T (Box 144, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings, Combined Meeting of the Western Forest Nursery Associations: Western Forest Nursery Council, Forest Nursery Association of British Columbia, and Intermountain Forest Nursery Association. Held in Vernon, British Columbia, August 8-11, 1988. Fort Collins, Colorado: USDA Forest Service, Rocky Mountain Forest and Range Experiment Station, December 1988; Formerly Box 64T (Box 144, Folder 7)
    - Proceedings of the 1976 Southeastern Area Nurserymen's Conferences. Held in Charleston, South Carolina, August 3-5, 1976 and in Mobile, Alabama, August 17-19, 1976, Formerly Box 64U (Box 145, Folder 1)
    - Proceedings of the Southeastern Area Forest Tree Nurserymen's Conference. Held in Greenville, Mississippi, July 24-26, 1972 and in Wilmington, North Carolina, August 7-10, 1972, Formerly Box 64U (Box 145, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the 1980 Southern Nursery Conference. Held in Lake Barkley, Kentucky, September 2-4, 1980, Formerly Box 64U (Box 145, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings of the Southeastern Area Forest Nurserymen Conferences. Held in Stone Mountain, Georgia, August 28-29, 1968 and in Alexandria, Louisiana, September 10-11, 1968, April, 1969; Formerly Box 64U (Box 145, Folder 4)
    - Proceedings of the Southeastern Nurserymen's Conference. Held in Lake Barkley, State Resort Park, Cadiz, Kentucky, July 27-29, 1970, Formerly Box 64U (Box 145, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings: 1982 Southern Nursery Conferences. Held in Oklahoma City, Oklahoma, August 9-12, 1982 and in Savannah, Georgia, July 12-15, 1982, Formerly Box 64U (Box 145, Folder 6)
    - Proceedings of the 1978 Southern Nursery Conferences. Held in Hot Springs, Arkansas, July 24-27, 1978 and in Colonial Williamsburg, Virginia, August 7-10, 1978, Formerly Box 64U (Box 145, Folder 7)
    - Abstracts of Papers Presented at the International Symposium on Applications of Biotechnology to Tree Culture, Protection and Utilization. Held in Columbus, Ohio, August 5-8, 1991. Edited by Bruce E. Haissig, T. Kent Kirk, William L. Olsen, Kenneth F. Raffa, and James M. Slavicek. Radnor, Pennsylvania: Northeastern Forest Experiment Station, July, 1991; Formerly Box 64U (Box 145, Folder 8)
    - Control of Shoot Growth in Trees: Proceedings of the Joint Workshop of IUFRO Working Parties on Xylem and Shoot Growth Physiology. Held in Fredericton, New Brunswick, Canada, July 1980. Compiled and Edited by C.H.A. Little. Fredericton, New Brunswick: Maritimes Forest Research Centre, [no date], Formerly Box 64V (Box 146, Folder 1)
  - Wood--Emphasis Biomass
    - Forest Biomass Studies. Orono, Maine: Life Sciences and Agriculture Experiment Station, University of Maine, 1971; Formerly Box 64V (Box 146, Folder 2)
    - Kyoto Biomass Studies. Presented by the International Union of Forest Research Organizations S4.1 Mensuration Growth and Yield Working Party on Forest Biomass. Orono, Maine: Complete Tree Institute of the School of Forest Resources, University of Maine, November, 1981; Formerly Box 64V (Box 146, Folder 3)
    - Biological and Sociological Basis for a Rational Use of Forest Resources for Energy and Organics. Proceedings of an International Workshop held at Michigan State University, May 6-11, 1979. Asheville, North Carolina: Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, Formerly Box 64V (Box 146, Folder 4)
    - Materials Aspects of World Energy Needs. Washington, D.C.: National Academy of Sciences, 1980; Formerly Box 64V (Box 146, Folder 5)
    - Wood: An Energy Source for the Southern Appalachian Highlands. Edited by Raymond S. Ferell. Proceedings of a Workshop sponsored by the Southern Appalachian Research/Resource Management Cooperative (SAR/RMC). Cullowhee, North Carolina: Western Carolina University, 1978; Formerly Box 64V (Box 146, Folder 6)
  - Wood Properties
    - Utilization of the Changing Wood Resource in the Southern United States. Symposium. Raleigh, NC: North Carolina State University, 1984; Formerly Box 64V (Box 146, Folder 7)
    - Lightwood Research Coordinating Council. Compiled by Robert N. Stone, Jacksonville, Florida: Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Products Laboratory, USDA - Forest Service, 1984; Formerly Box 64V (Box 146, Folder 8)
    - SFTIC -23rd Southern Forest Tree Improvement Conference. Asheville, NC: The Southern Forest Tree Improvement Committee, 1995; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 1)
    - Esser, Mary H. Lightwood Research Coordinating Council. Atlantic Beach, Florida: Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Products Laboratory, USDA - Forest Service, 1978; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 2)
    - Esser, Mary H. Lightwood Research Coordinating Council. Atlantic Beach, Florida: Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Products Laboratory, USDA - Forest Service, 1977; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 3)
    - Esser, Mary H. Lightwood Research Coordinating Council. Jacksonville, Florida: Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Products Laboratory, USDA - Forest Service, 1976; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 4)
    - Density... a Key to Wood Quality. Symposium. Madison, Wisconsin: Forest Products Laboratory, Forest Service, US Department of Agriculture, 1965; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 5)
    - Impacts of Changing Quality of Timber Resources. Edited by Richard Porterfield and John B. Crist. Madison, Wisconsin: Forest Products Research Society, 1978; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 6)
    - Complete Tree Utilization of Southern Pine. Edited by Charles W. McMillin. New Orleans, Louisiana: Forest Products Research Society, 1978; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 7)
    - Esser, Mary H. Lightwood Research Coordinating Council. Atlantic Beach, Florida: Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, Forest Products Laboratory, USDA - Forest Service, 1979; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 8)
    - Silva Fennica. Edited by Seppo Oja,. Vol. 16 No. 2 Society of Forestry in Finland., 1982; Formerly Box 64W (Box 147, Folder 9)
    - Synopsis of Wood Symposium, held by the Plus Tree Board of the Tree Farm Forestry Committee, November 2, 1961 (Box 383, Folder 14)
  - Wood Utilization
    - Proceedings: The International Union of Forestry Research Organisations Division 5 Conference. Held in Madison, Wisconsin, June 27-July 5, 1983., Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 1)
    - Abstracts: The International Union of Forestry Research Organisations Division 5 Conference. Held in Madison, Wisconsin, June 27-July 5, 1983., Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the Fiber Conservation & Utilization Seminar. Sponsored by Pulp & Paper magazine, Chicago, Illinois, May 29-31, 1974. San Francisco, California: Pulp & Paper, 1975; Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 3)
    - Programme: The International Union of Forestry Research Organisations Division 5 Conference. Held in Oxford, April 8-16, 1980, Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 4)
    - Better Wood Products through Science. Proceedings of All-Division 5 Conference "Forest Products." Held in Nancy, France, August 23-28, 1992. Volume 2. International Union of Forestry Research Organizations., Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 5)
    - Timber Management Toward Wood Quality and End-Product Value. Proceedings of CTIA/IUFRO International Wood Quality Workshop, Quebec City, Canada, August 18-22, 1997. Edited by S.Y. Zhang, R. Gosselin, and G. Chauret. Sainte-Foy, Canada: Forintek Canada Corp, Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 6)
    - Abstracts of the Forest Products Research Society 30th Annual Meeting. Held in Toronto, Canada, July 11-16, 1976. Madison, Wisconsin: Forest Products Research Society, [no date], Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 7)
    - Abstracts of Papers to be Presented at the Eighth Cellulose Conference: Wood Chemicals-A Future Challenge. Held in Syracuse, New York, May 19-23, 1975. SUNY College of Environmental Science and Forestry, [no date], Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 8)
    - 1975 International Paper Physics Conference. Held in Ellenville, NY, September 21-25, 1975. TAPPI, Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 9)
    - Impacts of the Changing Quality of Timber Resources. Proceedings of a joint meeting of the Economics & Financial Management and Timber Production Technical Committees of the Forest Products Research Society, 1978 Annual Meeting, Atlanta, Georgia, June 28, 1978. Edited by Richard L. Porterfield and John B. Crist. Madison, Wisconsin: Forest Products Research Society, Formerly Box 64X (Box 148, Folder 10)
    - Proceedings of Southern Plantation Wood Quality Workshop. Held in Athens, Georgia, June 6-7, 1989. Asheville, NC: Southeastern Forest Experiment Station, June, 1990; Formerly Box 64Y (Box 149, Folder 1)
    - A Technical Workshop: Juvenile Wood-What Does It Mean to Forest Management and Forest Products? Proceedings. Madison, Wisconsin: Forest Products Research Society, 1986; Formerly Box 64Y (Box 149, Folder 2)
    - Proceedings of the Symposium on the Effect of Growth Acceleration on the Properties of Wood. Held in Madison, Wisconsin, November 10-11, 1971. Forest Products Laboratory, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1972; Formerly Box 64Y (Box 149, Folder 3)
    - Proceedings: 1975 International Paper Physics Conference. Held in Ellenville, NY, September 21-25, 1975. TAPPI, Formerly Box 64Y (Box 149, Folder 4)
    - Energy Technologies and Policies for North Carolina: Conference Proceedings, May 1978. Environmental Studies Council, University of North Carolina, [no date], Formerly Box 64Y (Box 149, Folder 5)
    - Proceedings of the Symposium on the Effect of Growth Acceleration on the Properties of Wood. Held in Madison, Wisconsin, November 10-11, 1971. Forest Products Laboratory, Forest Service, U.S. Department of Agriculture, 1972; Formerly Box 64Y (Box 149, Folder 6)
    - Abstracts of Forest Products Research Society, 32nd Annual Meeting, held at Atlanta, June 25-30, 1978 (Box 383, Folder 15)
  - World Forestry Conferences
    - Papers 1-22, FAO Technical Conference on Exploration, Utilization and Conservation of Plant Gene Resources. Held in Rome, September 18-26, 1967. [unpublished, homemade bound collection of papers], Formerly Box 64Y (Box 149, Folder 7)
    - Papers 23-42, FAO Technical Conference on Exploration, Utilization and Conservation of Plant Gene Resources. Held in Rome, September 18-26, 1967. [unpublished, homemade bound collection of papers], Formerly Box 64Z (Box 150, Folder 1)